Brian P. Huhn

CONTACT:

Mobile Phone: (513)-335-1810Email: huhnbrian@gmail.com

Mr. Huhn has over 5 years of experience in Software Engineering. He is experienced in multiple forms of software development cycles including kanban, devOps, agile, and SysDev. He is well-versed in object oriented programming, software design, unit testing, database management, algorithms, embedded systems, and typescript frameworks. Mr. Huhn has a strong understanding of node package manager libraries such as karma, express, and Nodejsin addition to frameworks such as vue, angular, react, and react Native.

EDUCATION

• B.S. Computer Engineering, University of Toledo, 2021

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Booz Allen Hamilton, March 2023 - Present Senior Software Engineer

From March 2023 to present Mr. Huhn has contributed to contracts for the Veteran Benefits Management System for the Department of Veteran Affairs. Here he:

- Collaborated with fellow senior developers to deliver code in a timely and efficient manner.
- Ensured all code was 508 compliant
- Maintained test cases to follow 100% code coverage
- Worked with UI/UX designers to create wireframes that follow the customer requirements as well as maintain ADA compliance
- Maintained pipelines for deployments

Ball Aerospace & Technologies Corp., July 2021 - March 2023 Software Engineer II

From July 2021 to March 2023 Mr. Huhn has been a member of the Mission and Platform (M&P) Sustainment team. Here he develops multiple ATEP II projects. As a developer his activities included:

- Maintaining, Developing, and Debugging software originally developed by different teams across NASIC
- Implementing features requested by customers
- Creating unit and integration tests to prevent errors from getting into the factory
- Performed demonstrations for customers

London Computer Systems, May 2019 - August 2019 Applications QA Intern

From May 2019 to August 2019 Mr. Huhn worked as Quality Assurance for the Rent Management software innovation team. As a QA he:

- Tested code for the innovation team's Rent Management software
- Deployed code to factory if the software passed his inspections
- Presented finalized products to investors in the presence of the company's founder
- Attended seminars that trained him in all forms of real estate management

Ridge Tool Company, August 2018 - April 2019 Full Stack Engineer Intern

From August 2018 to April 2019 Mr. Huhn developed websites for companies bought by Emerson. As a stack engineer he:

- Created/Updated Emerson's webpages as well as their subsidiaries
- Deployed Greenlee.com
- Maintained websites previously deployed by his team
- Created Widgets for Emerson's web developers
- Updated databases to follow domain requirements
- Tested and Reviewed co-workers' code prior to deployment
- Deployed code to factory

EXPERIENCE IN SPECIFIC AREAS

Computer Skills

Programming Languages	Python, Javascript/Typescript, Java, Go, C++, C# Bash, Shell, golang
Version Control Systems	Git
Integrated Development Environments	Visual Studio Code, Netbeans
Database Management Systems	Elasticsearch, Postgres, Nodejs, express, SQL
Operating Systems	Windows 10/11, WSL, CentOs, Ubuntu
Frameworks	React, React Native, Angular, Vue, Django, Jira, Fitnesse
Markup Languages	HTML5, XML,YML
Office Automation Packages	Jenkins, Confluence